♪Looking in the mirror,
my temples have turned white♪
♪Taking off the hairpins and makeup,
shedding the disguise♪
♪A cold face♪
♪With two lines of tears♪
♪If an actor could gain pity♪
♪The audience offers sincere words♪
♪Perhaps the story could be changed♪
♪The storyteller says♪
♪This mortal world is full of turmoil♪
♪Within sight but beyond reach♪
♪Yet I still don't want to give up♪
♪Don't let the memory be hollowed out♪
♪Don't make me ridiculous♪
♪Some vows turn into smoke
and fade away♪
♪Even the leaves know when autumn comes,
but you don't even know me♪
♪Imprisoned in plight,
yet still full of passion♪
♪I mock this absurd and entangled love♪
♪How can I bear to let go♪
=Whispers of Southern Song=
=Episode 24=
Xu You'an, my good son.
You can't run away this time.
Where is the treasure map?
Right here.
See if you have what it takes to get it.
If you hand over the treasure map,
kneel, and beg for mercy,
for the sake of our many years of bond,
I will grant you a decent death.
Then for the rest of your life,
don't even think about
finding that treasure map.
Wait.
We can't let him off so easily.
I want to watch him die slowly.
You go first.
I'll cover the rear.
Or neither of us will survive.
Xu You'an,
we promised to live and die together.
If you die alone,
you'll break your promise again.
Do you want me to live in guilt
for the rest of my life?
♪Helpless situations♪
♪Overwhelmed by time♪
♪Even if I have questions♪
♪I harbor desires♪
Alright, you take the Buddha Head
and go to the meeting place
with Chun'er.
I promise you
we'll all live on well together.
♪Wandering around♪
♪Fortunate to have you with me♪
♪Go through the entanglement♪
♪If longing♪
♪Turns into dust and smoke♪
♪How can I be at ease♪
♪Having walked through prosperous times♪
♪And travelled around the world♪
♪Scars all over me♪
♪If longing never fades♪
♪Burns still hot♪
Xu You'an.
♪After half a lifetime of loneliness♪
♪In the next life♪
♪Entangle with you again♪
♪If longing♪
♪Turns into dust and smoke♪
♪How can I be at ease♪
♪Having walked through prosperous times♪
♪And travelled around the world♪
♪Scars all over me♪
♪If longing never fades♪
♪Burns still hot♪
♪Let it turn into dust and smoke♪
(Rong Xiaonan, you must
make it out alive.)
Xu You'an,
stop trying to act tough.
Hand over the treasure map,
and you may still live on.
Or I'll kill you immediately.
When father and son talk,
outsiders have no place
to interrupt. Right?
My son,
now it's just you and me.
You can tell me now, right?
You actually killed him?
What about your deal?
He was nothing at all.
I've long wanted to kill him.
Without him,
I can trade with the Japanese directly
and get much more.
As for you, hand over
the treasure map obediently.
And I will let you continue
being our family's watchdog.
Speak.
Where is the treasure map?
Devils belong in the hell.
I said
that I'll take care of you till the end.
Don't shoot.
Xu You'an! Xu You'an!
(How many orphans)
(in this chaotic world got to live...)
Xu You'an!
(Like I did?)
(I once had a brother too.)
(If he were still alive,)
(he would probably look just like you.)
Let's make this place
our home from now on.
♪Let it turn into dust and smoke♪
♪After half a lifetime of loneliness♪
Brother!
You want me dead?
It's not that easy.
♪Without entering the garden♪
♪How can I know the beauty of spring♪
♪Looking in the mirror,
my temples have turned white♪
♪Taking off the hairpins and makeup,
shedding the disguise♪
♪A cold face♪
♪With two lines of tears♪
(And Chun'er, you'll be our backup.)
(Get there before dawn.)
(If the Jade Buddha Head is there,)
(no matter what happens to us,)
(take the Jade Buddha Head
and leave first.)
♪The storyteller says♪
♪This mortal world is full of turmoil♪
♪Within sight but beyond reach♪
♪Gorgeous purples♪
♪And brilliant reds♪
Still daring to sing opera here?
Now take this.
♪And brilliant reds bloom♪
Speak. Where is the treasure map?
♪It turns out♪
Mr. Rong, you're no longer needed.
How dare you deceive me!
♪Looking in the mirror,
my temples have turned white♪
♪Taking off the hairpins and makeup,
shedding the disguise♪
♪A cold face♪
(Xu You'an,)
(you said,)
(though the ceremony was not completed,)
(we are still family.)
(I remember what you said.)
(Mr. Rong,)
(I'll see the world beyond the stage)
(for you.)
(I will rewrite all those
tedious opera scripts.)
(I'll write a piece of Po Zhen Zi,)
(not about the one
in the boudoir's dream)
(but about the Vermilion Bird
reborn from fire,)
(holding the sun in its beak
and flying into the daylight.)
♪Even the leaves know when autumn comes,
but you don't even know me♪
- Great!
♪It turns out♪
♪Gorgeous purples♪
♪And brilliant reds bloom everywhere♪
Everyone's here.
Welcome.
Welcome to our
Dreammaker Murder Mystery Club.
We'll play the script
"Whispers of Southern Song".
(Whispers of Southern Song)
Now, let me introduce
the story background.
During the era of Republic of China,
warlords ruled,
and conspiracies lurked
behind the prosperity.
In this magical age
of interwoven extravagance and gunfire,
heroic tales unfolded in the chaos.
Shitou and Zhuzi
were both orphans wandering the streets.
With similar fates,
they called each other brothers
and clung to each other
in the turbulent times,
living a life of wandering and hardship.
♪Trapped in dawn and dusk♪
♪Candle by the west window♪
♪Burned out this life♪
♪Ending in nothingness♪
♪I ask why♪
♪I yearn for the one who's gone
through heat and cold♪
♪A handful of earth♪
♪The world's last gamble♪
♪Sighing at the late hour♪
♪No one comes to meet me♪
♪As if it were fate♪
♪Deliberately playing tricks♪
♪We miss each other♪
♪Creating a turbulent drama♪
♪And a bizarre♪
♪Anonymous legend♪
♪The plot twists and turns♪
♪Play out over and over again♪
♪Waiting to be discarded♪
♪And you are like a moth to the flame♪
♪Refuse to submit♪
♪I can't bear to blame you♪
♪There are always too many♪
♪Helpless situations♪
♪Overwhelmed by time♪
♪Even if I have questions♪
♪I harbor desires♪
♪Nowhere to find answers♪
♪People come and go♪
♪I'm still all alone♪
♪Wandering around♪
♪Fortunate to have you with me♪
♪Go through the entanglement♪
♪If longing♪
♪Turns into dust and smoke♪
♪How can I be at ease♪
♪Having walked through prosperous times♪
♪And travelled around the world♪
♪Scars all over me♪
♪If longing never fades♪
♪Burns still hot♪
♪Let it turn into dust and smoke♪
♪After half a lifetime of loneliness♪
♪In the next life♪
♪Entangle with you again♪